Review,Entities Found
It isn't of downloading anything. I my as well have a $4 pay as you go phone. Oh but it's in really nice condition.,"[('4', 'MONEY')]"
ITS SO GOOD!! SASDFYGYkygvcjytjytfytyctjtfhayjf! No ? OK BYE.,"[('SASDFYGYkygvcjytjytfytyctjtfhayjf', 'ORDINAL')]"
This phone worked for what I was looking for. I got a fourth line free from T-Mobile for a promotion and all lines have unlimited data. Turns out you cannot easily use a tablet on a phone sim or a pho...,"[('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('T-Mobile', 'ORG'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('200', 'MONEY'), ('130', 'MONEY'), ('500-$800', 'MONEY'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('USA T-Mobile', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
"Granted, this is an older model, but I prefer to hold at least the semblance of a phone next to my ear than a wanna be iPad (iPhone 6 and others). The format was easy to learn: I also use Mac computer...","[('iPad', 'ORG'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mac', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Kindle', 'PERSON'), ('300+', 'DATE'), ('Solfeggio', 'ORG'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('AT&T', 'ORG'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('No Contract', 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('AT&T', 'ORG'), ('monthly', 'DATE'), ('less than $50.Another', 'MONEY'), ('every month', 'DATE'), ('CON', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Android', 'ORG'), ('Apple', 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
"Needed a quick backup phone, and this could get to me the fasted, otherwise I would have gotten a nokia. It works in a pinch, but NO predictive text! So texting is a slow nightmare. Signal strength is...","[('22', 'MONEY'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('one weekend', 'DATE')]"
Only 2g it does not work on 3g or 4g,"[('Only 2', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
"This is the second ASUS phone bought, but I am disappointed now because the phone is defective, most of the time when any app is open or close, the screen goes black, or sometimes the window for the a...","[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('ASUS', 'ORG')]"
Phone came in excellent condition. Shipping was quicker than posted. I got this phone for my son who broke his old one.....as of now he seems pleased with his replacement. Also came with the usb cable...,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('usb', 'ORG')]"
